Guide to the Office of University Development records, 1947-ongoing UA.14.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Office of University Development records
1947-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Office of University Development
UA.14.02.0001
49 Linear Feet
1 Gigabytes
The Office of University Development is responsible for fund-raising programs in the areas of annual gifts, capital gifts, and program support. This collection contains printed promotional materials and annual reports as well as fund-raising materials such as mailings to alumni and parents. Additionally, there are VHS tapes and a DVD. There are a small number of photographs in this collection as well as questionnaires and gift records. The materials range in date 1947-ongoing.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The Office of University Development records were received by the University Archives as transfers over a period of time.
Biographical/Historical note
The Office of University Development is responsible for fund-raising programs in the areas of annual gifts, capital gifts, and program support. The Gifts Records Office acknowledges all gifts to the University and maintains the official records on them, as well as the permanent files on all endowment funds. This office was formed in the Fall of 1981 by a merger of the gift record functions of the Alumni, Development, and Institutional Advancement Offices. The purpose of this merger was to centralize gift record functions. Development activities in the professional schools and in other areas of the University coordinate with and report to the Development Office.
Scope and Contents note
Contains materials created and distributed by the Office of University Development in the promotion of the University and its programs in fund-raising efforts. This collection includes promotional materials, annual reports/plans, and a website archive, Campaign for Duke, as well as fund-raising materials such as mailings to alumni and parents. Additionally, there are VHS tapes and a DVD. There are a small number of photographs in this collection as well as questionnaires and gift records. The materials range in date 1947-ongoing.
Related Material
Office of Institutional Advancement Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Alumni Affairs Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Conditions Governing Access
Records including the personal information of individual donors to the University will be closed for a period of 70 years.
Duke University. School of Law -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University. School of Medicine -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University. Trinity College of Arts and Sciences -- Funds and scholarships; Duke University. Office of Alumni Affairs; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Endowments -- Periodicals; Duke University. Office of University Development; Duke University. School of Forestry; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Duke University -- Handbooks, manuals, etc.; Duke University. Capital Campaign for the Arts and Sciences; Duke University. Alumni Association; Duke University. Department of Alumni Affairs; Duke University -- Endowments; Duke University. Divinity School; Duke University -- Funds and scholarships
- Loyalty Fund Campaign, 1947-1977
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains accessions A75-77 and A92-58.
  - The Loyalty Fund, 1948-1959 (Box 1)
  - The Duke University Loyalty Fund Campaign, 1947-1948 (Box 1)
  - The Duke University Loyalty Fund Campaign, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents, 1948-1949 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - November Letters, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Third Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - April Letters, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - Area Campaign, 1949-1950 (Box 1)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings and Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Medical Agents' Mailings and Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Medical Parents' Mailings, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Fund Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings and Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Undivided Classes, 1957-1958 (Box 1)
  - Anniversary/Gift Programs, 1943-1958 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents, 1953-1974 (Box 1)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Fund Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Fund Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Class Agents' Mailings, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Fund Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Loyalty Fund Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Pace Setters List and Enclosures, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Divinity School Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Law School Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Forestry School Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Medical School Mailings, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Fund Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Class Agents' Mailings: All Schools and Colleges, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Giant Step Campaigns, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Fund Report, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Undergraduate Loyalty Fund Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Law School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Divinity School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Forestry School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Medical School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Loyalty Fund Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Pace Setters, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Undergraduate Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Law School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Divinity School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Forestry School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Progress Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Pace Setters, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Undergraduate Loyalty Fund Mailing, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Law School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Forestry School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Medical School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - General Information for Class Agents, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Undergraduate Loyalty Fund Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Law School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Divinity School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Forestry School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Medical School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Graduate School Mailings, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous [papers from 1969-1970 intermingled here], 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Loyalty Fund Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Divinity Class Agents, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - Class Agents, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Undergraduate 1942, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1942, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Undergraduate 1942, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1943, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1943, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1917, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1918, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Undergraduate 1957, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1957, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Law 1957, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1920, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1921, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1945, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1945, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1945, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1922, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1946, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1946, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1946, 1969-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1947, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1947, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1947, 1971-1972 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Class of 1961, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1961, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1961, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Law 1961, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Medical 1960, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Law 1960, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary Gift Programs: Divinity 1960, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Class Agents and Loyalty Fund, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Loyalty Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Loyalty Fund, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, Campaigns, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Class Agents and Mailings, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- University Development Reunion Questionnaires, 1983-1987
  Series includes accession A93-80.
  - Class of 1928-Class of 1945 (Box 5)
  - Class of 1946-Class of 1959 (Box 6)
  - Class of 1959-Class of 1966 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1967-Class of 1973 (Box 8)
  - Class of 1974-Class of 1982 (Box 9)
- Capital Campaign, 1950-2004
  Series includes accessions A81-109, A92-113, A98-93, and A2005-0008.
  - Duke University Development Campaign Records, 1950-1959 (Box 10)
  - Clippings, 1984-1992 (Box 10)
  - Mailings, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Fleishman, Joel: Outrageous Ambitions... A Report, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Fleishman, Joel: Report to the Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Fleishman, Joel: Report to the Board of Trustees, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Planning, 1988 (Box 10)
  - The Duke Steuben Project, 1990 (Box 10)
  - Susan B. King: Founder's Day, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Mailing Lists, 1990 RESTRICTED (Box 10)
  - Campaign Kickoff Documents, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Campaign Kickoff Photos, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Trustees Resolution, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Invitation/Packet, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Symposium, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Remarks by President Keohane at Campaign for Duke Meeting, 1998 (Box 10)
  - VHS: Campaign for Duke Town Meeting, 1998 (Box 10)
  - Campaign for Duke, 1998-2004 folders as follows:
    - Athletics (Box 10)
    - Bench Mark [newsletter] (Box 10)
    - Comprehensive Cancer Center (Box 10)
    - Campaign DVD and VHS (Box 10)
    - Divinity School (Box 10)
    - Duke Magazine (Box 10)
    - DUMC (Box 10)
    - School of Engineering (Box 10)
    - Fuqua (Box 10)
    - Identity Standards Model (Box 10)
    - School of Law (Box 10)
    - Libraries (Box 10)
    - Medical School (Box 10)
    - Nasher Museum of Art (Box 10)
    - NSOE (Box 10)
    - School of Nursing (Box 10)
    - Portrait (Box 10)
    - Trinity (Box 10)
    - University and Health System (Box 10)
    - Regional Campaign Councils Handbook (Box 10)
- Capital Campaign Printed Matter, 1965-2003
  Series includes accessions A75-177, A95-69, A92-113, A95-74, and materials with an unknown provenance.
  - Gift Planning, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Capital Gifts to Duke University, 1974-1980, 1982-1984 (Box 11)
  - Overview: The Loyalty Fund Report, 1979-1982 (Box 11)
  - Overview: The Duke University Annual Fund Report, 1982-1986 (Box 11)
  - Duke Annual Fund Report and Special Reunion Tribute, Happy 40th Birthday, 1986-1987 (Box 11)
  - Duke Annual Fund Report and Special Reunion Tribute, 1987-1988 (Box 11)
  - Duke: To Cross a Threshold, circa 1980s (Box 11)
  - Pamphlets, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - A Special Tribute: Class Reunion Gifts, 1981-1983 (Box 11)
  - For the Future of Duke, undated (Box 11)
  - Gifts, Grants and Contracts to Duke University, 1980-1982 (Box 11)
  - Duke Parents' Letter, 1983-1988 (Box 11)
  - Planned Philanthropy... For the Future of Duke, 1973-1979, 1983, 1987, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Quadrangle, 1984-1985, 1991 (Box 11)
  - Guide for Volunteers, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Outrageous Ambitions: Duke 2000 The Society of Centurions, undated (Box 11)
  - Honor Rolls, 1990-1992 (Box 11)
  - The Campaign for Duke Booklet, 1990 (Box 11)
  - The Campaign for Duke Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 11)
  - A Community Pledged to Posterity, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Brochures: Endowments, Scholarships and Funds, undated (Box 11)
  - Centers and Programs, undated (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Matter, 1979-2003 (Box 11)
- Gift Records/Endowment Funds, 1950-2001
  Series includes accessions A79-51, A93-57, A94-125, A96-4, A88-16, A95-69, A96-125, UA2011-0015 and materials with an unknown provenance.
  - Endowment Funds, 1964-1988 (Box 12)
    - Folder 1: A (Box 12)
    - Folder 2: B (Box 12)
    - Folder 3: C (Box 12)
    - Folder 4: D-F (Box 12)
    - Folder 5: G (Box 12)
    - Folder 6: H (Box 12)
    - Folder 7: I-L (Box 12)
    - Folder 8: Mc-M (Box 12)
    - Folder 9: N-S (Box 12)
    - Folder 10: T-Z (Box 12)
  - Annual Giving Loyalty Fund Report, 1950 (Box 12)
  - C. S. Douglas Fund - "The Peacemaking Mentality" by Anna G. Douglas [Typescript], circa 1957 (Box 12)
  - C. S. Douglas Fund -- "Field Study of Peacemaking in the U.N." by Anna Douglas, circa 1957? (Box 12)
  - C. S. Douglas Fund, 1984-1993 "In Honor of Those Who Enable Learning" Banquet Programs, 1979-1981 (Box 12)
  - Plan of Acton Reports, Andrew D. Parker, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Plan of Action Report, 1983 (Box 12)
  - Washington Duke Club, 1980-1989 (Box 12)
  - William Preston Few Association, 1983-circa 1989 (Box 12)
  - William Preston Few Association and Washington Duke Club Gift Club Directory, 1986-1988 (Box 12)
  - Annual Fund Calendar, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Office of Gift Records: Policy Manual, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Memoranda, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Reports: Three Year Comparative Report, 1994 RESTRICTED (Box 12)
  - Duke Views Screen Saver, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Announcements, Invitations, etc., 1999 (Box 12)
  - Duke Annual Fund Executive Committee, late 1970s-early 1980s (7 folders) (Box 28)
  - Duke Annual Fund Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
- Electronic Materials, 1981-2008
  Conditions Governing Access
  Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
  Scope and Contents
  Series includes accessions UA2005-0033 and UA2009-0002.
  - Annual Fund Plans, Reports, and Analyses, 1981-2008; 49 PDF files; approximately 215 megabytes.
    [Restricted until 2033]
  - Campaign for Duke Website, 1997-2005; 1 disk image derived from optical disk; approximately 763 megabytes. (Box 27)
- Miscellaneous/Oversize Materials
  Series includes accessions A84-49, A92-58, A94-109, A95-69, A2005-0001, A2002-12, A2005-0033, and UA2009-0010.
  - Printed Materials (Box 13)
    - The Chronicle, 1998 Oct. 5 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for Duke School of Engineering, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for Duke University Libraries, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for Duke University Medical Center, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for the Divinity School, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for Duke Chapel, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for the School of Law, circa 1998 (Box 13)
    - The Campaign for Duke, circa 1998 (Box 13)
  - Printed Material (Box 14)
    - Duke Campaign Thresholds, 1985-1991, copies 1-2 (Box 14)
    - Campaign Report, 1990, 1990/1991 (Box 14)
    - The Campaign for Duke: A Final Report, June 1992 (Box 14)
  - Printed Material and Miscellaneous (Box 15)
    - The Duke Honor Roll, 1991/1992, 1993/1994 (Box 15)
    - Interview with Charles A. Dukes, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Duke University Foundation Handbook for Faculty and Staff, 1971 (Box 15)
    - Proposed Perkins Memorial Plaques, Ink Drawings (Box 15)
    - Hart Report, 1966 (Box 15)
  - Gift Records/History of Funds, 1896-1971 (Box 16-23)
    - Volume 1 (Box 16)
    - Volume 2 (Box 17)
    - Volume 3 (Box 18)
    - Volume 4 (Box 19)
    - Volume 5 (Box 20)
    - Volume 6 (Box 21)
    - Volume 7 (Box 22)
    - Volume 8 (Box 23)
  - Scrapbook (Box 24)
  - Scrapbook (Box 25)
  - Volunteer Solicitor Training videocassette, undated (Box 26)
  - Duke Seminar Task Force Report, 1994 (Box 26)
  - Final Report of the Task Force on Prospect Management and Regionalization, 1994 (Box 26)
  - Task Force Recommendations, 1994 (Box 26)
  - Hinkle, Marion, 1994 (Box 26)
  - The Science Resource Initiative, undated (Box 26)
  - Time Capsule (non-circulating) (Box 27)
- Accession UA2018.0048, 1
  - Donor Feedback, 2006-2007 (Box 40)
    Donor information restricted until 2077.
  - Annual Reports, 1985; 1991-1993; 1996 (Box 40)
  - Annual Reports, 2004-2008 (Box 40)
  - Invitations (Box 40)
  - Invitations, 2004-2008 (Box 40)
  - Reports/Action Plans (Box 40)
  - Affording Opportunity: Financial Aid Initative (Box 40)
    Contains a CD with files
  - Gifts to Duke, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
- Accession UA2018.0058, 2
  - Presidents invitations, earlier years (Box 29)
  - Recruitment invitation (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Reunion Volunteer recruitment cards (Box 29)
  - Reunions invitations, 2008-2009 (Box 29)
  - Duke Annual Fund invitation, President's Council (Box 29)
    unfoldered
  - Duke Reunions Honor Roll, 2008 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Reunion Honor Roll, 2007 (Box 29)
  - Honor Roll of Reunion Donors, 2005-2006 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Thanksgiving and Birthday cards, 2001 (Box 29)
  - Birthday cards (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund, 2007 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund holiday cards, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund/RHB letter, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Duke Annual Fund Cornerstone (Box 29)
  - Cornerstone Decal, Annual Fund, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Cornerstone calendar/card, 2005 (Box 29)
  - Cornerstone brochure insert, 2005 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Thanksgiving, 2009 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Thanksgiving, 2007 (Box 29)
  - Thank you card, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Honor Roll, 2005 (Box 29)
    on CD-R
  - Honor Roll, 2004 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund leadership brochure (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund leadership brochure, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund leadership benefits card (Box 29)
  - Homecoming invitations, 2005 (Box 29)
  - Homecoming invitations, 2001 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund cornerstone ad, 2004 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund cornerstone brochure, 2004 (Box 29)
  - Cornerstone certificate, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Cornerstone insert, 2006 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence (Box 29)
    [unfoldered]
  - Annual Fund gift club ad in Duke Magazine, 2004 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund big donor ad, 2003 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Duke Magazine ad, 2002 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund volunteer recognition ad, Duke Magazine, 2001 (Box 29)
  - Volunteer manual (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Washington Duke Club letters (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund half page ad, 2008 (Box 29)
  - Duke Magazine "Stephanie" ad (Box 29)
  - Duke Magazine "Scan Dot" ad, 2010 (Box 29)
  - untitled, 2007 (Box 29)
  - untitled (Box 29)
  - Contact sheet for advertisement (Box 29)
  - untitled (Box 29)
  - Parent class chair letters, spring 2007 (Box 29)
  - Parent committee letter, invitation to join, 2007 (Box 29)
  - Calender year end mailing, 2007 (Box 29)
  - End of year package, 2006 (Box 29)
  - End of year card, 2005 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund video series, 2009 (Box 29)
  - Student thank you cards, 2009 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund subscriptions, 2014 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund young alumni honor rolls, 2008 (Box 29)
  - Duke story reprint, spring 2007 (Box 29)
  - William Preston Few, 2003-2004 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Reunion invites, 2002 (Box 29)
  - Preston Few Invites, 2002 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund Few Society Invites, 2001 (Box 29)
  - Annual Fund gift club brochure, 2004 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous invitations, samples; Duke University in Europe (Box 29)
  - Scholarship dinner samples (Box 30)
  - Jewish Life at Duke (Box 30)
  - Gardens (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund honor roll samples (Box 30)
  - University Development samples (Box 30)
  - Brochure samples (Box 30)
  - Duke Alumni Association reunion samples (Box 30)
  - Recognition Weekend samples (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund reunion samples (redesign) (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund reunion samples (before redesign) (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund mailer samples (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund Lybunt brochure (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund Lybunt, 2008 (Box 30)
  - Lybunt Annual Fund, Spring 2007 (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund Reunion leadership receptions (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund parent mailer, 2005 (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund parent address card, 2004 (Box 30)
  - Annual Fund address cards, 2001 (Box 30)
  - Campaign for Duke materials (Box 31)
  - C2C (Coast to Coast) at Duke (Box 31)
  - Annuity Ads, 2006 (Box 31)
  - Annuity Ads, 2005 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning ads, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning playbill ad, 2003 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning annuity update, 2002 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning ads, Bill Quick, 2005 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine, January-February 2008 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning ad, Charlie Blanchard, March-April 2008 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine (Smiths), May-June 2008 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine (Ricks and Hodges), July-August 2008 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine (Spears), September-October 2008 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning series (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine, gift planning, 2010 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine, January-February 2009 (Box 31)
  - untitled, March-April 2009 (Box 31)
  - untitled, May-June 2009 (Box 31)
  - untitled, July-August 2009 (Box 31)
  - untitled, September-October 2009 (Box 31)
  - Duke Magazine (Bunting and Randolph), November-December 2008 (Box 31)
  - Series (Box 31)
  - Planning giving general info (Box 31)
  - Planned giving brochures, 2001 (Box 31)
  - Gift records material, 2003 (Box 31)
  - Duke University planned giving folders (Box 31)
  - Charitable gifts, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Charitable reminder trust brochure and insert (Box 31)
  - Birthday cards (Box 31)
  - Holiday card, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning holiday card, 2006 (Box 31)
  - Holiday card, 2008 (Box 31)
  - End of year card, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Gift planning year end postcard 2007 (Box 31)
  - Emeritus faculty event, 2008 (Box 31)
  - Legacy giving brochure, 2009 (Box 31)
  - Financially Speaking, 2008 (Box 31)
  - IRA rollover postcard, 2007 (Box 31)
  - Recognition Dinner, 2009 (Box 31)
  - J. B. Duke dinner, 2009 (Box 31)
  - Planned philathropy, 2008 (Box 31)